const webinarInfo1 = [
  "Introduction to AI tools and how they can be used to improve productivity.",
  "An overview of ChatGPT and how it can be used to generate text, translate languages, write different kinds of creative content, and answer your questions in an informative way.",
  "An overview of Dalle2 and how it can be used to create images, paintings, and other visual content.",
  "Examples of how AI tools can be used to save time in everyday tasks, such as research, writing, and creative work.",
  "Tips on how to choose the right AI tools for your needs.",
  "Tips on how to choose the right AI tools for your needs.",
  "Q&A session with the instructor.",
];
const webinarInfo2 = [
  "Personalized learning: 87% of K-12 teachers believe that AI can help personalize learning for students.",
  "Access to information: AI is expected to create 97 million new jobs by 2025, which will require workers with skills in areas such as data analysis, critical thinking, and creativity.",
  "Reduced workload: AI could automate up to 45% of tasks performed by knowledge workers.",
  "Improved engagement: Students who are engaged in their learning are more likely to persist in school and achieve their academic goals (University of Southern California).",
  "Improved learning outcomes: Students who use AI-powered learning tools perform better on exams than students who do not use these tools.",
];

const whyData = [
  "Geeks Of Gurukul offers a wide range of courses in various technology domains",
  "A team of instructors and mentors exclusively from the prestigious Indian Institutes of Technology (IITs).",
  "Personalized guidance to each student.",
  "100% placement guarantee",
  "Personalized guidance to each student.",
  "High quality learning",
];

const pricingBenifits = [
  "Gain a comprehensive understanding of AI tools and their applications",
  "Explore the capabilities of ChatGPT, ",
  "Discover the potential of DALL",
  "Understand the time-saving benefits of AI tools",
  "Learn to choose the right AI tools",
  "Gain access to the Internet's first 'Tech with AI' Blueprint",
  "Learn about the rising demand for Techies with AI skills, potential salary ranges & career paths",
  "Understand how ChatGPT enhances traditional UX design methods",
  "Dive deep into the future of UX Design with AI and explore its cutting-edge applications",
];

const accordionData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "Is the workshop certified?",
    answer:
      "Yes, the workshop is certified. Participants will receive a certificate of completion upon successfully attending and completing the workshop.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What should I be prepared with before the workshop starts?",
    answer:
      "Before the workshop starts, it is recommended to have a stable internet connection, a device (computer or laptop) with a webcam and microphone, and any necessary software or tools as communicated by the organisers. It's also helpful to have a notebook and pen for taking notes during the session.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "When is the workshop?",
    answer:
      "The workshop is scheduled for Wednesday, May 24, 2023 at 2.00 pm.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Can AI tools replace human creativity?",
    answer:
      "AI tools are powerful assistants that can enhance creativity, but they are not intended to replace human creativity. Instead, they can provide inspiration, generate ideas, and assist in creative processes.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Are these AI tools accessible to non-programmers?",
    answer:
      "Yes, many AI tools are designed to be user-friendly and do not require programming knowledge. The webinar will highlight user-friendly AI tools that can be utilized by non-programmers.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Will there be practical demonstrations during the webinar?",
    answer:
      "Yes, the webinar will include practical demonstrations to showcase the capabilities and functionalities of AI tools, allowing participants to observe their usage in action.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Do I need any prior knowledge or technical expertise to attend this webinar?",
    answer:
      "Do I need any prior knowledge or technical expertise to attend this webinar?",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "I made the payment but didn't receive any email.",
    answer:
      "Please write to us at support@geeksofgurukul.com. Our awesome support team will get back to you as soon as possible.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Will there be opportunities for interactive participation, such as asking que or engaging in discussions?",
    answer:
      "Yes, absolutely! The webinar will provide opportunities for interactive participation, including asking questions. There will be a Q&A session at the end of the webinar.Â  We value your input and encourage active participation from all attendees.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Is there a limit on the number of questions I can ask during the Q&A session?",
    answer:
      "No, there is no limit on the number of questions you can ask during the Q&A session. We encourage active participation and value your curiosity.",
  },
];

export { webinarInfo1, webinarInfo2, whyData, pricingBenifits, accordionData };
